So now let's actually practice this a little bit.
所以现在让我们实际练习一下。
I'm going to give you part of a synopsis synopsis is a basic overview basic outline of what happened
我要给你一个概要的一部分概要是一个基本概述发生了什么的基本概述
in a movie or a TV series.
在电影或电视剧中。
OK we're just going to do that for a little bit.
好的，我们只做一点。
A short one and then I'm going to also include some of my opinions about it.
一个简短的，然后我还将包括一些我对它的看法。
We're going to use some of the words and phrases that we've learned in this lesson.
我们将使用我们在本课中学到的一些单词和短语。
And we're also going to describe how we feel about different parts of this particular TV series.
我们还将描述我们对这部特定电视剧的不同部分的感受。
So here's the example.
所以这里是例子。
SIMON X plays so Simon x is the actor right.
西蒙 X 扮演所以西蒙 x 是正确的演员。
Simon x plays a heartbroken doctor named Kyle a heartbroken doctor named kyle in the new series.
西蒙x在新系列中扮演一个名叫凯尔的伤心医生，一个名叫凯尔的伤心医生。
Blah blah blah blah.
哈哈哈哈哈哈。
Have you ever heard of blah blah blah blah.
你有没有听说过胡说八道。
That's good.
那挺好的。
At the start of the series he is struggling to cope with the death of his wife cope with means deal
在系列开始时，他正在努力应对妻子的死亡应对手段交易
with if somebody dies that's very painful.
如果有人死了，那是非常痛苦的。
It's very sad right.
非常可悲吧。
If you cope with it you're dealing with that loss.
如果你应付它，你正在处理这种损失。
He's struggling to cope with the death of his wife.
他正在努力应对妻子的去世。
Anyway he gets a new job at a good hospital.
不管怎样，他在一家好医院找到了一份新工作。
So we're just giving some details what happens.
所以我们只是提供了一些细节。
Basically this is what we would call a synopsis.
基本上这就是我们所说的概要。
He gets a new job at a good hospital and gets a reputation for being very fair minded and caring.
他在一家好医院找到了一份新工作，并以非常公正和关怀而闻名。
So now we can say something about his character.
所以现在我们可以谈谈他的性格了。
Now we're talking about who he is.
现在我们正在谈论他是谁。
Now we go into a bit of a review because the best part about this series is him right.
现在我们进行一些评论，因为这个系列最好的部分是他是对的。
And so we can talk about why we like him.
所以我们可以谈谈为什么我们喜欢他。
He's a really likable main character.
他是一个非常讨人喜欢的主角。
And even though his story is quite tragic tragic means very sad very sad story even though his story
尽管他的故事很悲惨 悲惨意味着非常悲伤 非常悲伤的故事 即使他的故事
is quite tragic.
相当悲惨。
He's got a great sense of humor.
他很有幽默感。
That means he's funny.
这意味着他很有趣。
That doesn't mean it's a comedy.
这并不意味着它是一部喜剧。
It just means he's funny.
这只是意味着他很有趣。
Maybe it's a drama but he is funny.
也许这是一部戏剧，但他很有趣。
He's got a great sense of humor.
他很有幽默感。
He's always quick to use a sarcastic remark with his colleagues a sarcastic remark sarcasm is or sarcasm
他总是很快地对他的同事使用讽刺的话
is a very important part of American humor and other humor I guess in an English speaking culture.
是美国幽默和其他幽默的一个非常重要的部分，我猜想在英语文化中。
So basically it means something bad happened and I say Oh great.
所以基本上这意味着发生了一些不好的事情，我说哦，太好了。
So you kind of say the opposite thing to what you really mean.
所以你说的与你真正的意思相反。
OK so a sarcastic remark with his colleagues the people he works with.
好吧，对他的同事和他一起工作的人说一句讽刺的话。
So we've kind of mixed here the synopsis or a little bit of a synopsis.
所以我们在这里混合了概要或一些概要。
What happens with the reason we liked the series which is the main character he's a likable main character.
我们喜欢这个系列的原因是什么，他是一个讨人喜欢的主角。
And then we talk about why that is maybe because of his own loss.
然后我们谈论为什么这可能是因为他自己的损失。
He's able to sympathize with people who are struggling and console them.
他能够同情和安慰那些挣扎的人。
So to sympathize means you understand how other people feel.
所以同情意味着你理解别人的感受。
You show them that you care about them.
你向他们表明你关心他们。
You sympathize with them.
你同情他们。
You feel there may be pain they're suffering their sorrow and console them if you console someone you
如果你安慰你的人，你会感到他们正在忍受他们的悲伤并安慰他们
make them feel better or you try to make them feel better.
让他们感觉更好，或者你试着让他们感觉更好。
It's ok you can console people in many different ways but that's what it means to try to make them feel
没关系，你可以用许多不同的方式来安慰别人，但这就是试图让他们感觉到的意义
better.
更好的。
So my favorite part of the whole series is his character.
所以整个系列中我最喜欢的部分是他的角色。
That's what I like about it.
这就是我喜欢它的地方。
My favorite part of the whole series is his character.
整个系列中我最喜欢的部分是他的角色。
The only thing I don't really like is that many of the episode plots are a bit repetitive and predictable.
我唯一不喜欢的是很多情节情节有点重复e 和可预测的。
So that means maybe every one every story is different.
所以这意味着也许每个人每个故事都是不同的。
Same characters but sometimes what happens in each episode is too similar to what happened in a previous
相同的角色，但有时每一集中发生的事情与前一集中发生的事情太相似了
episode.
插曲。
So I feel like OK I've already seen this kind of story.
所以我觉得我已经看过这种故事了。
It's getting a bit repetitive that means something happens again and again it repeats it's very predictable.
它变得有点重复，这意味着某些事情会一次又一次地重复，这是非常可预测的。
If you can predict something it means you know what's going to happen next.
如果您可以预测某事，则意味着您知道接下来会发生什么。
It is a bit predictable predictable.
这是一个有点可预测的预测。
I would still recommend it though I would still recommend it though.
我仍然会推荐它，尽管我仍然会推荐它。
That means even though there is something I don't like about it I like it enough to say that you should
这意味着即使有一些我不喜欢它的地方，我也很喜欢它，可以说你应该
watch it.
看它。
I would still recommend it.
我仍然会推荐它。
OK so this is just a simple example of a basic synopsis and a review of why we like the series and something
好的，这只是一个基本概要的简单示例，并回顾了我们为什么喜欢该系列之类的东西 关于我们为什么不喜欢它。
All right.
好的。
So to really get a feeling for this you can talk with your friends about it but first you should practice
因此，要真正了解这一点，您可以与您的朋友谈论它，但首先您应该练习
it so you can do it maybe as a recording or if you have a friend you can talk with movie's about.
这样您就可以将其作为录音进行，或者如果您有朋友可以谈论电影。
Try it with them.
和他们一起试试。
I want you to talk about a TV series or movie that you've seen recently.
我想让你谈谈你最近看过的电视剧或电影。
Explain the premise or the basic story what it's about without giving away every detail.
在不泄露每个细节的情况下解释前提或基本故事。
So just do a basic synopsis of the story OK.
所以只要对故事做一个基本的概要就可以了。
And then also describe the main character and some of the good things and the bad things some of the
然后还描述了主角和一些好的东西和一些不好的东西
positives and the negatives about the story.
故事的正面和负面。
I practice this and when you get used to describing movies and saying what you like and what you don't
我练习这个，当你习惯于描述电影并说出你喜欢和不喜欢的东西时
like you'll find it a lot easier to have discussions with friends about movies and TV and that's one
就像您会发现与朋友讨论电影和电视一样容易得多，这就是其中之一
of the most common topics there is which people like to talk about.
最常见的话题中有人们喜欢谈论的话题。
Correct.
正确的。
All right.
好的。
Good luck.
祝你好运。